Guide to the National Organization for Women, New York City Chapter (NOW-NYC) Records TAM.106
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Committees, 1966-2006; 1970-2002; 19.58 Linear Feet in 41 manuscript boxes, a flat box, 3 oversized flat boxes, and 2 flat-file-folders
  - Psychology and Psychotherapy Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Psychology and Psychotherapy Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Psychology and Psychotherapy Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1971-1984 (Box 112, Folder 10-11)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Public Relations Committee -- Clippings, April - June 1974 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Public Relations Committee -- How to Make the Media Work For You, 1974 (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Public Relations Committee -- "How To" Press Kits, 1984-1987 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Public Relations Committee -- Information About, 1985 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Public Relations Committee -- Press Contacts, undated (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - Rape Prevention Committee, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Rape Prevention Committee, 1973-1990 (Box 113, Folder 1-3)
  - Rape Prevention Committee, January - June 1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Rape Prevention Committee, July - December 1974 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Rape Prevention Committee, January - June 1975 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Rape Prevention Committee, July - December 1975 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Rape Prevention Committee, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Rape Prevention Committee, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Rape Prevention Committee, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Rape Prevention Committee, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Binder Materials, 1974-1976 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Eliminating Statute of Limitations on Rape, 2006 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Event Flyers, 1988-1989 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Focus 15, circa 1974 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Grant Applications, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Joan Little Case, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Library (Folder 1 of 2), 1971-1977 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Library (Folder 2 of 2), 1971-1977 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Martin Evans Rape Trial, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Mayor's Task Force on Rape, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Mayor's Task Force on Rape, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Membership, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Minutes, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Minutes, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Minutes, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Newsletter, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Petitions, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Questionnaires, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- "Rape, the Law, and You" Broadcast Transcript, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- "Rape, the Law, and You" Notes, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Rape Speakers Bureau, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Rape Victims, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Research -- Self Defense, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- United Nations Force in Cypress -- Report of Turkish Atrocities, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- WABC and Roger Grimsby's Special Report on Rape, 1980 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- "What Every Woman Should Know About Rape", 1981 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Rape Prevention Committee -- Women's Walk Against Rape, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Reproduction and its Control Committee, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Reproduction and its Control Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Reproduction and its Control Committee, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee, 1979-1998 (Box 113, Folder 8-9)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Abortion, 1971-1991 (Box 114, Folder 1-5)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Abortion and the 1984 Election (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Abortion Rights Forum, 1979-1980 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Administrative, 1987 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Alcohol Related Fetal Protection Bill, 1991 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- A Contraceptive Ripoff: A Study of Birth Control Pill Prices in Manhattan, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Correspondence, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Crisis Pregnancy Center Probe, 2002 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Event Flyers, 1989-2002 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Fertility, 2002 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- International Day of Action for Reproductive Rights, 1981 (Box 115, Folder 8, Box 153, Folder 11)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Legal Precedents and Legislative Bills on Abortion with NOW Annotations, 1989-1990 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Legislation, 1987-1990 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Operation Rescue and Project Defend, 1988-1989 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Parental Consent Bill and Pro-Choice, 1989-1992 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Press Releases, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Pro-Choice Rally, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Reproductive Rights Resource Kit, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Resources, 1979 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- RU 486, 1990 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Slogans, undated (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Sterilization, 1978 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Reproductive Rights Committee -- Title X and Family Planning, 1982 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Sex Education, Contraception, and Abortion Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Sexism in Religion Committee, 1970-1976 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Sexuality Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Sexuality Committee -- Feminist Sexuality Project, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Sexuality Committee -- Women's Sexuality Conference, June 9-10, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Sexuality Committee -- Women's Sexuality Conference, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Sexuality and Lesbianism Committee, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Sexuality and Lesbianism Committee -- Feminist Sexuality Project Questionnaire, 1971 (Box 153, Folder 21)
  - Sexuality and Interpersonal Relations Committee, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Sexuality and Interpersonal Relationships Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Structural Review Task Force, 2001 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Textbook Committee, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Women in Prison Committee, 2002 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Writers Committee, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Young Women and Girls Committee, 2002 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Youth NOW Committee, 1979, 1982 (Box 116, Folder 16)
- Series V: Programs, 1967-2019; 1977-2002; 5.06 Linear Feet in 11 manuscript boxes and an oversized flat box
  This series focuses on events and projects hosted by NOW–NYC that do not fall under the jurisdiction of a specific committee. These programs range from the broad multi-issue "Women Strike for Equality March" (1971) to the narrower-focused "Endowed Chair" project (1973-1976), through which NOW named its conference room chairs after renowned women in history. This series contains conference and convention materials including information packets, agendas, and programs; invitations, programs, budgets, correspondence, and agendas related to the Women of Power Influence Awards; postcards related to the Women's History Series; and invitations, programs, budgets, correspondence, and agendas related to the Susan B. Anthony Awards.
  Materials in this series are listed in alphabetical order by program.
  - 10th Anniversary Gala Banquet, 1977 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - "Abortion Rights and the 1984 Election" Program (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Around-the-Clock Watch for the ERA, 1979-1980 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Assertiveness Training Workshop, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - August 26th Packet, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - AWARE day fair, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Benefit for Battered Women, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Bike-a-Thon, 1981 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Cable Television Series, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Celebrate Women!: A Benefit for NOW-NYC, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Celebration Night with NOW-NYC, 1984 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Central Park Attack Anniversary Rally, 2002 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Conferences and Conventions, 2012-2016 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Conference on Families, 1979-1980 (Box 117, Folder 5-6)
  - Conference on Women's Liberation, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Constitutional Convention on the Bill of Rights and Suffrage, 1967 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - District 37 Conference on Women and Work, 1982 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Emergency Campaign for Women's Lives March and Rally, 1991 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Emergency March for Women's Lives, 2001 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Employment Law Clinic, 1996-1997 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Empowering Women Present Elayne Booster at the Town Hall, 1991 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Endowed Chair Project, 1973, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Equality in Mortgage Lending--articles, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - ERA Walk-A-Thon, 1981 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Event Flyers, 1971-1990, 2002 (Box 117, Folder 14, Box 118, Folder 1-2)
  - Feminist Action and Leadership on College Campuses Event, 2002 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Feminist Community Press Conference, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Feminist Holiday Fairs, 1971-1978 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - First Day Covers, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Global Sweatshop Coalition Rally, 2002 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - "Have Women Achieved Full Equality…or Do We Still Need Feminism" Panel, 2002 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Herstory Project, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - International Women's Day, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - International Women's Day, 1978-1984 (Box 118, Folder 7-13)
  - International Women's Day March and Rally, circa 1970s (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - International Women's Year (1975), 1973-1975 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - International Women's Year, 1977 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Leadership Training Workshop--December 13, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Lesbian-Gay Pride March, 1985 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Let Them Eat Cake Sale and Rally, 1983 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Lobby Day, 1989 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - March for Equality, 1971 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - March for Freedom of Choice, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - March for Women's Lives, 1992, 2004 (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - March on Washington for Jobs, Peace, and Freedom, 1983 (Box 118, Folder 21, Box 153, Folder 13)
  - Merrill Lynch Protest, 2000 (Box 118, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous documents, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Mother's Day Bill of Rights, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 14, Box 118, Folder 23)
  - Mother's Day Rally, 1985 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Mother's Day Speakout on Child Care, 1983 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Moving Forward Party, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - National March for Women's Lives, 1986 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - National NOW Conference -- Denver, CO -- "Toxic Tax Syndrome", 1986 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - NOW's 30th Anniversary Reunion, 1997 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - NOW-NYC's 2007 Campaign: Ending the Business of Trafficking in New York City (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - NOW-NYC Chapter Development Day, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - NOW-NYC Employment Law Clinic, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - NOW-NYC Office Re-Opening Event, 1984 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - NOW Women in Comedy Awards, 1991 (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - NYC Women's Leadership Summit, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Opening New Doors: A Sales Career Conference for Women, 1980 (Box 119, Folder 12-13)
  - Operation Rescue Protest (Buffalo, NY), 1992 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Planned Parenthood Protest, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Protest at Democratic Mini-Convention in Philadelphia, 1982 (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Public Speaking Workshop, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Reforming Due Process Violations at the New York State Division of Human Rights, 2001 (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - Saks Fifth Avenue Boycott, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Saks Fifth Avenue Protest, 1996 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - Seize the Internet: NOW World, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Speakers, 1971-1979 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Street Sign Unveiling for Susan B. Anthony and Elizabeth Cady Stanton, undated (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 1980-1981, 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 22-28)
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 1984, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 1994, 1998, 2002, 2006 (Box 120, Folder 1-4)
  - Susan B. Anthony Awards, 1994-2010 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Tenth Anniversary Gala Banquet--March 25, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Town Hall Celebration of the Arts, January 10-February 14, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Town Hall "Dialogue on Women's Liberation", 1971 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Urban Woman's Conference, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 27, Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Urban Woman Project, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Urban Woman Project -- Report on Referral System, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Urban Woman Project -- The Urban Woman Resource Guide, 1978 (Box 120, Folder 8-9, Box 153, Folder 14)
  - Urban Woman Project -- Waterfront Commission, 1980 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Washington Labor Day March, 1981 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Womanpower Project, 1979-1981 (Box 23, Folder 28, Box 121, Folder 1-2)
  - Womanpower Project -- Attorney Referral Lists, 1979-1990 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Womanpower Project -- Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Womanpower Project -- Description, undated (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Womanpower Project -- Lawyer's Seminar, 1978-1979 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Womanpower Project -- Legal Resources and Reference Materials (Family Relations), 1987 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Womanpower Project -- Monthly Progress Reports, 1978-1981 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Womanpower Project -- North Star Funding Application, 1979 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Womanpower Project -- NOW-NYC's Recommendation to the NYC Commission on the Status of Women, undated (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Womanpower Project -- Report on Referral System by Mary Mycio, 1981 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Womanpower Project -- Women on the Waterfront Project, undated (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Women and AIDS: Exploring the Issues, Jan 28, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Women's City Club Gala, 1981 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - Women's Conference on Education for Liberation, 1971 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Women's Equality Day, 1981-1982, 1984 (Box 123, Folder 1-3)
  - Women's Equality Pay Day Rally, 1985 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Women's Equality Week, 1977-1978 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Women Fighting Poverty Conference, 1996, 2002 (Box 123, Folder 6-7)
  - Women's Film Program, 1972-1975 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Women's Health Conference, NYC, Nov. 18-21, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Women's History Series, 1980-1981 (Box 106, Folder 1-6)
  - Women and Law Conference, 1985 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Women March for Equality, August 26, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 31, Box 123, Folder 9, Box 153, Folder 18)
  - Women March for Justice and Equality, August 26, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Women Photographers NOW, 1991 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Women: A Political Force Conference, November 13-14, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 29, Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Women of Power and Influence Awards, 1995-2019 (Box 105, Folder 4-7, Box 122, Folder 7-13)
  - Women's Rights Day, 1971 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Women's Rights Day in Congress, 1981 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Women's Sexuality Conference, 1974 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Women Strike for Equality, August 26, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 30, Box 123, Folder 13-14)
  - Women's Strike for Justice and Equality, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Women of Vision Awards, 1982-2001 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - World March of Women, 2000 (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - Youth/NOW, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Series VI: National and Regional NOW, 1966-2008; 1970-2002; 7.94 Linear Feet in 17 manuscript boxes and 2 oversized flat boxes
  Materials in this series focus upon various branches of NOW and NOW-NYC including National NOW; regional NOW branches; NOW New York State (NOW-NYS); local chapters; the Service Fund of NOW-NYC, a charitable and educational organization that operates a variety of projects, programs, and services on behalf of NOW-NYC; the Legal Defense and Education Fund, the nation's first legal defense and education fund for women; and the WomanPower PAC, a political action committee created so NOW could legally work in election campaigns at the state and local level. The WomanPower PAC eventually evolved into the PAC of NOW-NYC. This series contains budgets, agendas, memorandums, press statements, event flyers, conference materials, directories, and information packets produced by different branches of NOW and NOW-NYC.
  Materials in this series are arranged by chapter or region, starting with the largest organizing group to smallest. Materials are arranged alphabetically by topic and then chronologically, when applicable.
  - National NOW, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - National NOW, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - National NOW, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - National NOW, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - National NOW, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - National NOW, January - June 1973 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - National NOW, July-December 1973 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - National NOW, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - National NOW, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - National NOW, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - National NOW, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - National NOW, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - National NOW, 1979, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - National NOW -- Administrative Papers, 1970, 1979 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - National NOW -- Bill of Rights, 1968 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - National NOW -- Board Directories, 1978-1979 (Box 124, Folder 3, Box 33, Folder 2)
  - National NOW -- Board Meeting Minutes, 1979-1981, 1983-1984, 2000-2002 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - National NOW -- Bylaws, 1983 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - National NOW -- Chapter Actions, circa 1980s (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - National NOW -- Child Care Task Force, 1970 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - National NOW -- Conference, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - National NOW -- The First Five Years, 1966-1971 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - National NOW -- Fundraising, 1971-1973 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - National NOW -- Memorandum, 1978-1980, 1983-1984 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - National NOW -- National Conference (Washington, D.C.), 1966-1967 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - National NOW -- National Conference (Atlanta, GA), 1968 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - National NOW -- National Conference (Chicago, IL), 1970 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - National NOW -- National Conference (Los Angeles, CA), 1971 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - National NOW -- National Conference (Washington, D.C.), 1972-1973 (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - National NOW -- National Conference (Philadelphia, PA), 1975 (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - National NOW -- National Conference (Detroit, MI), 1977 (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - National NOW -- National Conference (New Orleans, LA), 1985 (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - National NOW -- National Conference (New York, NY), 1991 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - National NOW -- National Conference (30th Anniversary), 1996 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - National NOW -- National Conference (Rochester, NY), 1998 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - National NOW -- National Conference (Philadelphia, PA), 2001 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - National NOW -- National Conference (St. Paul, MN), 2002 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - National NOW -- NOW Foundation, undated (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - National NOW -- Origins and History, undated (Box 24, Folder 10, Box 127, Folder 7)
  - National NOW -- Policy Manual, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - National NOW -- Programs for NOW: Task Force Summaries, 1973 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - National NOW -- Statements by Eleanor Smeal, 1979 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - National NOW -- Task Force on Rape Prevention, 1973-1976 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - National NOW -- Task Force on University Compliance, 1973 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - National NOW -- Tomorrow is NOW (Summary of NOW's Existing Resolutions and Policies), 1971-1972 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - National NOW -- "Write On!: A Handbook for Effective Letter Writing", circa 1970s (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Central Region, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Eastern Region, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Eastern Region, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Eastern Region, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Eastern Region -- Auction for Action Convention, 1973 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Eastern Region -- Wonderwomen Conference (Atlantic City, NJ), 1974 (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Northeast Region, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Northeast Region, 1983, 2000-2003 (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - Northeast Region -- NOW Conferences, 1972, 1983, 2002 (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - Western Region, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - NOW New York State, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - NOW New York State, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - NOW New York State, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - NOW New York State, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - NOW New York State, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - NOW New York State, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - NOW New York State, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - NOW New York State, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - NOW New York State, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - NOW New York State, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - NOW New York State -- 1990 Gubernatorial Election, 1989-1990 (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - NOW New York State -- Annual Convention, 1984 (Box 125, Folder 19)
  - NOW New York State -- Conference on Marriage and Divorce, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 20)
  - NOW New York State -- Council Meetings, 1983-1987, 2000-2003 (Box 126, Folder 1-3)
  - NOW New York State -- Directories, 1982 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - NOW New York State -- Elections, 2002 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - NOW New York State -- Event Flyers, 1984 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - NOW New York State -- Family Relations, 1981, 1984-1986 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - NOW New York State -- Legislative Priorities, 1984-1988 (Box 126, Folder 8)